fanburst.com 2017-06-06

# Fanburst

_Your privacy is critically important to us. At Fanburst we have a few fundamental principles:_

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.

Doublenote LLC. (“Doublenote”) operates several websites including Fanburst.com. It is Fanburst’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Fanburst collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Fanburst’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Fanburst’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Fanburst may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Fanburst also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users who interact with Fanburst content. Fanburst only discloses IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Fanburst’s websites choose to interact with Fanburst in ways that require Fanburst to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Fanburst gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at Fanburst.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Fanburst are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Fanburst collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Fanburst. Fanburst does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

#### Aggregated Statistics

Fanburst may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Fanburst may monitor the most popular uploads on the Fanburst.com site or use comments to help identify spam. Fanburst may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Fanburst does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Fanburst discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Fanburst’s behalf or to provide services available at Fanburst’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Fanburst’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Fanburst will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Fanburst discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Fanburst believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Fanburst, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Fanburst website and have supplied your email address, Fanburst may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Fanburst and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Fanburst takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Fanburst uses cookies to help Fanburst identify and track visitors, their usage of Fanburst website, and their website access preferences. Fanburst visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Fanburst’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Fanburst’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Business Transfers

If Fanburst, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Fanburst goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Fanburst may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Fanburst may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Fanburst’s sole discretion. Fanburst encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
